Guide to the Harold T. Rib aerial photograph collection, 1930-1980
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
Harold T. Rib aerial photograph collection
1936-1979
C0236
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
12.5 linear feet (31 boxes)
31 boxes of aerial black and white photographs taken between the 1930s - 1979 of areas around the world, including the United States, Canada, Algeria, and Japan. Includes unprocessed oversize aerial photos.
Rib, Harold T.
Scope and Content
Aerial black and white photographs of various cities and towns in the United States as well Canada, Algeria, and Japan. Many of the photographs came from the private collection of Harold T. Rib, a professor and former chief of aerial surveys for the Bureau of Public Roads and the Federal Highway Administration. Includes unprocessed oversize aerial photos.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the George Mason University Department of Geography and GeoInformation Science in 2013.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Arrangement
Photographs are arranged alphabetically by country. Within each country folders are arranged alphabetically by state or province. Oversize photos are not currently arranged.
Historical Information
Aerial photography dates back to the 19th century and refers to photographs taken from an elevated position, usually in an aircraft. Geographical surveys are among the most common uses for these photographs.
Custodial History
This collection was originally created by Harold T. Rib, who donated it to the George Mason University Department of Geography and GeoInformation Science.
Related Material
Special Collections Research center also holds the
Index Terms
Geographical Names:
Algeria--Photographs.; Canada--Photographs.; Japan--Photographs.; United States--Photographs.
Document Types:
Aerial photographs.
Contents List
- Photographs, 1936-1979; (31 boxes)
  - Algeria, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Canada: British Columbia, 1952, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Canada: Extras, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Canada: General, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Canada: General, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Canada: Manitoba, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Northwest Territories, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Ontario, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Canada: Ontario, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Canada: Owen Sound, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Saskatchewan, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Canada: Quebec, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Japan: Hokkaido, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - USA: Alabama, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Grove Hill.
  - USA: Alabama, 1940-1942, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Chambers, Jefferson, Lauderdale, and Colbert.
  - USA: Alaska, 1947-1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - USA: Alaska, 1952-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - USA: Alaska, 1950-1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - USA: Alaska, 1948-1949, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - USA: Alaska, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Maps and notes.
  - USA: Alaska, 1948-1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photographed is Alaska in general and the Matanuska Valley.
  - USA: Alaska, 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - USA: Alaska, 1948-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - USA: Arizona, 1936-1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Apache, Coconino, and Navajo.
  - USA: Arizona, 1936, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Areas photographed include: Benson and San Francisco. Benson photographs are undated.
  - USA: Arkansas, 1968-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Boone, Clark, Franklin, Garland, Howard, Sevier, Logan, Marion, and Montgomery.
  - USA: Arkansas, 1950, 1971, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Counties photographed include: Perry and Pulaski.
  - USA: California, 1937, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Areas photographed include: Point Reyes and Yuba County.
  - USA: California, 1942-1955 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Counties photographed include: Inyo, Kern, Mono Lake, San Bernardino, and Sacramento.
  - USA: Colorado, 1938-1949, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Alamosa, Saguache, Boulder, and Puebelo.
  - USA: Colorado, 1937-1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Counties photographed include: Pueblo, Denver, Logan, San Miguel, Washington, and Weld.
  - USA: Connecticut, 1951-1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Areas photographed include: New Haven, Hartford County, and Litchfield.
  - USA: Delaware, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Rehoboth.
  - USA: Florida, 1948-1954, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Levy, Madison, Sarasota, and Suwannee.
  - USA: Florida, 1963, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Areas photographed include: Arran and Bradenton Beach.
  - USA: Florida, 1952, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Areas photographed include: Ellenton and Lake Apoka.
  - USA: Georgia, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of state. Areas photographed include: Atlanta and Dekalb County.
  - USA: Hawaii, 1963-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Hawaii, Maui, and Oahu.
  - USA: Idaho, 1939-1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Geologic map of state. Areas photographed include: San Tooth, Bingham County, Idaho County, Kootenai County, and Oneida County.
  - USA: Illinois/Indiana, 1969, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Vermillion County.
  - USA: Illinois, 1939-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: LaSalle, Clark, Iroquois, Wabash, and Will.
  - USA: Indiana, 1962-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Areas photographed include: Canaan and Cedarville.
  - USA: Indiana, 1971, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Areas photographed include: Loogootee and Metamora.
  - USA: Indiana, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Riverwood.
  - USA: Indiana, 1938-1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Clark, Decatur, Harrison, Lawrence, Marion, Monroe, Orange, and Porter.
  - USA: Iowa, 1938, 1968-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Counties photographed include: Allamakee, Clayton, Floyd, Lyon, Pottawattamie, and Winneshiek.
  - USA: Kansas, 1941-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Butler, Cowlay, Doniphan, Elk, Geary, Jefferson, Logan, Lyon, Scott, Thomas, and Trego.
  - USA: Kentucky, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Areas photographed include: Bernstadtt and Boltsfork.
  - USA: Kentucky, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Areas photographed include: Bowling Green and Cranston.
  - USA: Kentucky, 1939, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Areas photographed include: Cromwell, Hadley, Rockfield, and Mammoth Cave.
  - USA: Kentucky, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Areas photographed include: Morehead, Franklin, and Paintsville.
  - USA: Kentucky, 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Areas photographed include: Redbush, Sandy Hook, Sideview, and Upton.
  - USA: Kentucky, 1937-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Christian, Daviess, Edmonson, Fayette, Hart, McLean, and Lee.
  - USA: Landforms US Air Force, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - USA: Louisiana, 1950-1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of the state. Parishes photographed include: Beauregard and Vermilion.
  - USA: Maine, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Areas photographed include: Penobsco, Somerset County, and Augusta.
  - USA: Maryland, 1937-1952 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Counties photographed include: Allegany, Frederick, Garrett, Montgomery, and Washington.
  - USA: Maryland, 1963, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Areas photographed include: Baltimore and Kensington.
  - USA: Maryland, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Towson.
  - USA: Massachusetts, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Ayers Village.
  - USA: Massachusetts, 1939, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Geologic map of state. Areas photographed include: Brockton and Mt. Toby.
  - USA: Massachusetts, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Concord.
  - USA: Massachusetts, 1939, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Areas photographed include: Monson, Mt. Holyoke, and Southbridge.
  - USA: Michigan, 1943- 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Huron, Ingham, Keweenaw, and Marguette.
  - USA: Minnesota, 1938-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Carver, Goodhue, Hennepin, and Isanti.
  - USA: Minnesota, 1939-1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Counties photographed include: Lake, McLeod, Otter Tail, Olmsted, St. Louis, Scott, Swift, Todd, Wabasha, Wionna, Marshall, and Pack.
  - USA: Minnesota, 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Areas photographed include: Ely and Vergas.
  - USA: Minnesota, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Field Problems.
  - USA: Minnesota, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - USA: Minnesota, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - USA: Minnesota, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - USA: Mississippi, 1941-1942, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Geologic map of state. Areas photographed include: Chostaw County, Itawamba County, Lee County, Madison County, and Sumner.
  - USA: Missouri, 1938-1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Cole, Dent, Iron, Lincoln, McDonald, and Moniteau.
  - USA: Montana, 1954-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Custer, Judith Basin, Phillips, Roosevelt, Powder River, and Park.
  - USA: Nebraska, 1951-1955, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Cedar, Hitchcock, Holt, Kimball, Knox, Pierce, Sheridan, Sioux, Hayes, Cheyenne, and Cass.
  - USA: Nevada, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Lyon, Churchill, and Washo.
  - USA: New Hampshire, 1952-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Coos, Grafton, Hillsboro, and Strafford.
  - USA: New Jersey, 1940-1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Hunterdon and Middlesex.
  - USA: New Jersey, 1940-163 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Areas photographed include: Middlesex County, Ocean County, Somerset County, Ocean City, Sussex County, and Camden.
  - USA: New Mexico, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Sandoval County.
  - USA: New Mexico, 1941-1943 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Some of the photos are undated. Areas photographs include: Elephant Butte, San Pedro, and Wingate.
  - USA: New Mexico, 1939-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Chaves, Grant, Guadalupe, Hidalgo, Sallies Spring, and Sandoval.
  - USA: New York, 1936-1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Cattaraugas, Cortland, Greene, and Herkimer.
  - USA: New York, 1936-1966 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Counties photographed include: Niagara, Onondaga, Ontario, Schuyler, Cleming, Sullivan, Thompkins, and Wayne.
  - USA: New York, 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Counties photographed include: Saratoga, Rensselaer, and Albany.
  - USA: New York, 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Areas photographed include: Watervliet, Voorhesville, Schenectady, Selkirk, Albany County, and Bethlehem.
  - USA: New York, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Erie County.
  - USA: New York, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - USA: New York, 1959-1964, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Areas photographed include: Monbur, Wayne County, and Kingston.
  - USA: New York, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Counties photographed include: Onendaga and Madison.
  - USA: New York, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Poughkeepsie.
  - USA: New York, 1938, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Areas photographed include: Albany, Endicott, and Islip.
  - USA: New York, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - USA: New York, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - USA: New York, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - USA: New York, 1947, 1966, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Areas photographed include: Lawrence, Millbrook, and Newcomb.
  - USA: New York, 1947-1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - USA: New York, 1955-1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - USA: New York, 1960, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - USA: North Carolina, 1960-1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Geologic map of state. Areas photographed include: Catawaba County, Louisburg, and Robbins.
  - USA: North Dakota, 1938-1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: McHenry, Bowman, Burke, Burleigh, Cass, Cavalier, and Divide.
  - USA: North Dakota, 1938-1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Areas photographed include: Divide County, Kidder, Grand Forks, McHenry, McKenzie, Ward, and Larimore.
  - USA: Ohio, 1937, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Areas photographed include: Berea, Dayton, and Fairborn.
  - USA: Ohio, 1938-1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Geologic map of state. Photographed areas include: Clark County, Lorain County, and Wadsworth.
  - USA: Ohio, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Warren.
  - USA: Oklahoma, 1942-1956, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Atoka, Cimarron, Johnston, Leflare, Mayes, Okfuskee, and Pontotoc.
  - USA: Oklahoma, 1950-1956 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Counties photographed include: Pontotoc, Tulsa, and Texas.
  - USA: Oregon, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Dalles.
  - USA: Oregon, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Maps of the state.
  - USA: Oregon, 1942-1953, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed included: Coos, Jackson, Klamath, and Lane.
  - USA: Oregon, 1951-1955 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Counties photographed include: Lane, Marion, and Multnomah.
  - USA: Paw Paw, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - USA: Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    East Waterford.
  - USA: Pennsylvania, 1938-1939, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Areas photographed include: Harrisburg, Patton, and Pocono.
  - USA: Pennsylvania, 1938-1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of the state. Counties photographed include: Bedford, Berks, Blair, Bucks, Carbon, Centre, Chester, and Clinton.
  - USA: Pennsylvania, 1938-1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Counties photographed include: Columbia, Lycoming, Clinton, Erie, Fayette, Franklin, and Fulton.
  - USA: Pennsylvania, 1939-1964 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Counties photographed include: Greene, Jefferson, Lancaster, Lebanon, McKean, and Pike.
  - USA: Pennsylvania, 1940-1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Counties photographed include: Potter, Schuylkill, Susquehanna, Tioga, Washington, Westmoreland, York, Wyoming, and McKean
  - USA: Puerto Rico, 1963-1964, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Geologic map included.
  - USA: Puerto Rico, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - USA: Puerto Rico, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - USA: Rhode Island, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Counties photographed include: Kent, Providence, and Washington.
  - USA: South Carolina, 1972, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of state. Areas photographed include: Lancaster County and Greenwood.
  - USA: South Dakota, 1938, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Areas photographed include: Badlands, Spearfish, and Sturgis.
  - USA: South Dakota, 1938-1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Geologic map of the state. Counties photographed include: Codington, Custer, Davison, Fall River and Hughes.
  - USA: South Dakota, 1938-1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Counties photographed include: Hughes, Hutchinson, Lawrence, MarshallMeade, Mellette, Pennington, Shannon, and Stanley.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1938, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Areas photographed include: Hollow Springs and Martha.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969-1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of state. Counties photographed include: Cannon, Cumberland, Hawkins, Madison, and Putnam.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Counties photographed include: Carroll, Stewart, and Robertson.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Counties photographed included: Rutherford, Sumner, and Cumberland.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1949-1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Counties photographed include: Maury, Sullivan, Sumner, Campbell, Weakley, and Putnam.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1965-1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Counties photographed include: Stewart, Carter, Crockett, Cumberland, Sumner, and Hawkins.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Counties photographed include: Cumberland, Hawkins, Robertson, and Carter.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Counties photographed include: Tipton, Carroll, Carter, Robertson, and Sumner.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Counties photographed include: Sumner, Rutherford, and Union.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Counties photographed include: Sumner, Robertson, and Rutherford.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Robertson County.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Counties photographed include: Rutherford, Cannon, Tipton, Madison, and McNairy.
  - USA: Tennessee, 1969, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - USA: Texas, 1950-1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Geologic map of the state. Counties photographed include: Bexar, Brown, and Dallas.
  - USA: Texas, 1939-1954 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Areas photographed include: Laguna Vista, Dickens County, Dimmit County, Travis County, Potter County, Taylor County, Tarrant County, Motley County, and Reeves County.
  - USA: Texas, 1950-1955 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Counties photographed include: McLennan, El Paso, Galveston, Gillespie, and Lynn.
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1953, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - USA: Unknown Location, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - USA: Utah, 1938-1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Geologic map of the state. Photographed areas include Zion National Park and the following counties: Duchesne, Salt Lake, Wayne, Garfield, Box Elder, and Daggatt.
  - USA: Utah, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Photographed areas include: Acord Lakes, Marsh Park, and San Rafael.
  - USA: Vermont, 1939-1954 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Areas photographed include the following counties: Addison, Chittenden, Rockingham, Rutland, and Washington.
  - USA: Virginia, 1937, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Highway maps of Virginia. Photographs of Fairfax.
  - USA: Virginia, 1968-1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Photographed areas include: Beach, Washington County, and Richmond area.
  - USA: Virginia, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Dutch Gap.
  - USA: Virginia, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Fairfax.
  - USA: Virginia, 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - USA: Virginia, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Fairfax County (FFCo).
  - USA: Virginia, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - USA: Virginia, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - USA: Virginia, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - USA: Virginia, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - USA: Virginia, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - USA: Virginia, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - USA: Virginia, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - USA: Virginia, 1951-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Some photographs are of unknown areas. Other areas photographed include: Augusta County, Alexandria (Fairfax County), and Fairfax County.
  - USA: Virginia, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - USA: Virginia, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - USA: Virginia, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - USA: Virginia, 1954, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Areas photographed include: Fairfax, Lexington, and Prince George.
  - USA: Virginia, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Vienna.
  - USA: Virginia, 1978, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Vienna. Some of the photographs are undated.
  - USA: Washington, 1949-1978 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Geologic map of the state. Counties photographed include: Benton, Dalles, Lincoln, and Douglas.
  - USA: Washington, 1940-1955 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Counties photographed include: Douglas, Franklin, Grays Harbor, and Klickitat.
  - USA: Washington, 1941-1957 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Counties photographed include: Okanogan, Spokane, Thurston, Walla Walla, Whitman, and Yakima.
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1951 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1951 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1951 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1951 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1951 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - USA: Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - USA: West Virginia, 1939-1977 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Geologic map of the state. Counties photographed include: Berkeley, Gilmer, Grant, Jackson, Lewis, Kanawha, Mineral, Mingo, Pike, Tucker, and Arnoldsburg.
  - USA: Wisconsin, 1940-1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Geologic Map of the state. Areas photographed include: Fond du Lack County, Sheboygon County, Grant County, Jefferson County, Walworth County, Neenah, and Baraboro.
  - USA: Wyoming, 1937-1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Geologic Map of Wyoming. Counties photographed include: Albany, Campbell, Carbon, Fremont, Johnson, Laramie, Park, Sheridan, Sweetwater, and Grohnin.